UX/UI Designer

Passionate UX/UI designer with 3+ years of design experience in User Interaction and Web design, as well as demonstrated an understanding of the pace and variety of corporate work. Seeking to obtain a UX/UI designer position to help the organization with strategic thinking and collaborative design at every stage of the game, from research to wireframes to visual design.



Abilities



Illustration





Web Design



Responsive Design



Photography



Education

Interactive Media Design - 2018 to 2020

Post Graduation Algonquin college, Canada

Information and Technology - 2010 to 2014

Bachelor of Engineering Gujarat Technological University, India

Work Experiences

UX Designer Internship at TITUS Inc. - May 2019 to Aug 2019

- Worked on two major projects:
 - 1. Data Classification: Policy Manager
 - 2. Data Security: Illuminate Dashboard
- Designing wireframes and mockups
- Worked with UI designer to implement designs

Sr. Web Designer at LaNet Pvt. Ltd. - Dec 2015 to Dec 2018

- Worked on various graphics design projects
- Tools for designing, infographics, email design, Logo design
- Responsive tools, WordPress WooCommerce
- Worked on web design using Material design
- Used ¡Query for Web Animations like slider

Jr. Web Designer at Idea To Working - July 2014 to Nov 2015

- Meeting with client and gathering requirements
- Design and Develop web pages, also writing and editing web content
- How to fix the error with optimum use of code





Research

Prototyping - Wireframing - User Journey Product Behavior - Storyboarding - Survey Usability Testing- Persona - Cognitive Walkthrough



Collaboration

Self Starter - Detail-oriented Flexible - Communicative Responsive

Design

Adobe Photoshop - Adobe Illustrator - Adobe InDesign Adobe After Effects - Adobe Premiere Pro - Sketch - XD Adobe Lightroom - Spark - Canva



Programming

HTML5 - CSS3 - PHP - Javascript - JQuery - Angular JS - Keynote - Vue JS - ASP.Net - SCSS - LESS -BassCSS - BFM method

Introduction to HTML

Certificate / May 2018 – Present / License GREAUTN3GF58

Design - Applying Design Principles

Certificate / Jan 2018 - Present / License 206-10895623



Welcoming new students, Responsibility to provide accurate information about college

Purple Eye - The Design Studio

UI Design

User Experience Research, Personas, and User Scenario, Sitemap, Wireframing, Branding, Mood boards

Explore Ottawa – The capital of Canada

Wordpress

Created a small business website using a child theme, Product post and Contact form feature

iPhone - Apple

Drupal

Build in Drupal. Used a Sub theme to design and added features like product detail, SKU, blogs

Language Known







